sjs.co.nz 2016-01-22

# Privacy Policy | Student Job Search

### Introduction

We may collect, retain and use your personal information (including your e-mail address, name, phone number and mailing address) from time to time. This Privacy Policy sets out our practices regarding the collection, use, storage and disclosure of your personal information in compliance with the Privacy Act 1993. Please read this Privacy Policy before using this website or submitting your personal information to this website. By using this website, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. This privacy policy is subject to, and must be read in conjunction with, our Terms and Conditions.

### Terminology

In this Privacy Policy, the terms ‘SJS’, ‘we’, ‘us’, and ‘our’ refer to Student Job Search Aotearoa Inc and the terms ‘you’ and ‘your’ refer to you as a website user, student or employer.

### Information we may collect and retain

We may collect and retain your personal information in the following circumstances:

**a)** when you complete forms on this website (including surveys, search forms, competition entry forms, registration forms, job application forms and other forms);

**b)** when you create, modify, or use any accounts or registered user facilities available through this website; 

**c)** in the course of receiving questions, comments or other communications from you; and

**d)** as you navigate through this website, certain information may be passively collected (that is, gathered without your active participation) using various technologies and means, such as Internet Protocol addresses, cookies, Internet tags, and navigational data collection. Information collected may include server addresses, top-level domain names, dates and times of visits to the website, pages accessed and documents downloaded, previous websites visited and the type of browser used.

### Use of personal information

The personal information we collect will be used to provide services you have authorised or requested.  We may also use personal information collected by us to:

**a)** verify your identity and assist you in case you forget your password or login details

**b)** enable us to offer an effective employment job service and assist you in obtaining employment / employee referrals 

**c)** respond to any questions or correspondence from you;

**d)** manage and improve this website and any related services;

**e)** carry out internal research and development;

**f)** conduct student/employer satisfaction surveys via an independent agency to assist us better serve our clients;

**g)** provide you with information about a service that you are using (including critical updates and announcements);

**h)** reduce the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information;

**i)** customise this website to suit your particular preferences and interests;

**j)** where you create a message using this website (for the purpose of sending that message to us, or to any other recipient specified by you), send that message;

**k)** analyse website usage, trends and statistics;

**l)** with your permission, supply you with further information concerning products and services which may be of interest to you; or

**m)** carry out any other use that is authorised by you or is notified to you at the time of collection.

### Disclosure of personal information

We will not disclose your personal information except in accordance with this Privacy Policy (and in accordance with the Privacy Act 1993). We may use or disclose your personal information if you have authorised us to do so, or in any of the following circumstances:

**a)** we have given you notification of the intended use or disclosure and you have not objected to that use or disclosure;

**b)** you have consented for us to do so, we may provide your contact details to your past, current or prospective employers or employees;

**c)** you have consented for us to do so, we may provide your name and telephone number to students in the same job as you;

**d)** you apply for Job Seeker Support Student Hardship (JSSH) benefit from the Ministry of Social Development (MSD) and MSD request that we provide your SJS enrolment details (your personal information) in order to check your eligibility to receive the unemployment benefit or MSD request that we provide details of your use of our services, including jobs you have applied for or have attained;

**e)** we believe that the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to assist a law enforcement agency or an agency responsible for national security in the performance of their functions;

**f)** we believe that the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce any legal rights  we may have, or is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of you, us, or others; or

**g)** we are required or permitted by law to disclose the information.

### Third Party Websites

This website may contain hyperlinks to third party websites. We are not responsible for the content of such websites, or the manner in which those websites collect, store, use, and distribute any personal information you provide. When visiting a third party website from hyperlinks displayed on this website, we encourage you to review the privacy statements of those websites so that you can understand how the personal information you provide will be will collected, stored, used and distributed.

### Storage of personal information

Your personal information is collected by SJS and may be held by SJS and Simitive. These organisations’ addresses are set out below. The information collected on, or through, this website is stored on a secure SJS server located at the ICONZ Data Centre located at 60 Airedale Street, Auckland, New Zealand. In accordance with the Privacy Act 1993, SJS may store your personal information for as long as it may lawfully be used by SJS.

\- SJS: L8, Grand Annexe, 84 Boulcott St, Wellington, 6011

\- Simitive Limited: 2/318 Oriental Parade, Wellington, 6011

### Security

No data transmissions over the Internet are completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure the security of information transmitted from or to you. However, once we have received your personal information, we will use reasonable efforts to protect the information against loss or misuse, and against unauthorised access, use, modification, or disclosure.

### Right to access and correct your personal information

You may request access to, or correction of, any personal information we hold about you by contacting our privacy officer at: [privacy@sjs.co.nz](mailto:privacy@sjs.co.nz).

You have the right to access, request or correct the personal information that we hold about you at any time by accessing or editing the 'My Profile' details on this website.

To ensure that the personal information we hold about you is accurate and up to date, please update the 'MyProfile' page, or notify us of, any changes to your personal details as soon as possible.

If SJS does not agree to make a requested correction to your personal information, you have the right to request that we attach to the information a statement of the correction sought but not made.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to update, change or revise this Privacy Policy, at any time. Changes to this privacy policy will take effect immediately once they are published on this website. Please check the Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of this website or our services following the posting of any changes to the Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of those changes.

This Privacy Policy was last updated June 2013.

### Other Terms

Your use of this website is subject to our Terms and Conditions.
